Guide to the Edward Bradford Titchener papers,1887-1940.
Titchener, Edward Bradford papers, 1887-1940
- Correspondence
  - George Syrett (?) to EBT, 3/18/09 (Box 2)
  - C. W. Perky to EBT, 3/21/09 (Box 2)
  - George Syrett (?) to EBT, 3/21/09 (Box 2)
  - J, M. Cattell to EBT, 3/25/09 (Box 2)
  - George Syrett (?) to EBT Encl. contract, 4/6/09 (Box 2)
  - Mrs., A. L. Barnes to EBT, 4/24/09 (Box 2)
  - J. Mark Baldwin to EBT, 4/24/09 (Box 2)
  - Herbert Langfeld to EBT, 5/1/09 (Box 2)
  - H. John to EBT, 5/4/09 (Box 2)
  - Charles Judd to EBT, 5/10/09 (Box 2)
  - Wilson to EBT, 5/24/09 (Box 2)
  - ECS to EBT, 5/28/09 (Box 2)
  - J. Cartton Bell to EBT, 6/5/09 (Box 2)
  - Watson to EBT, 6/7/09 (Box 2)
  - Hinds, Noble & Eldridge to EBT, 6/9/09 (Box 2)
  - D. B. Williams to EBT, 6/10/09 (Box 2)
  - 0. S. Morgan to EBT, 6/11/09 (Box 2)
  - H. W. Carr to EBT, 6/12/09 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Nelson to EBT, 6/14/09 (Box 2)
  - Mary Calkins to EBT, 6/14/09 (Box 2)
  - Charles Bostwick to EBT, 6/18/09 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Nelson EBT, 6/19/09 (Box 2)
  - Wilson to EBT, 6/21/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 6/22/09 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Nelson to EBT, 6/22/09 (Box 2)
  - Mrs.., L. A. Pope to EBT, 6/23/09 (Box 2)
  - H, W. Carr to EBT, 6/25/09 (Box 2)
  - C. Stoelting to EBT, 6/25/09 (Box 2)
  - H. Ogden to EBT, 6/26/09 (Box 2)
  - Carl E. Seashore to EBT, 6/28/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 6/30/09 (Box 2)
  - Max Abell to EBT, 6/14/09 (Box 2)
  - Edwin Watkins to EBT, 7/6/09 (Box 2)
  - Stanley Gibbons to EBT, 7/13/09 (Box 2)
  - Macmillan to EBT, 7/14/09 (Box 2)
  - 4 receipts to EBT from Florence Chandler Publisher, 7/20/09 (Box 2)
  - Mrs.. L. A, Pope to EBT, 7/29/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 7/29/09 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Nelson to EBT End. statement of account, 8/3/09 (Box 2)
  - Hinds, Noble & Eldridge to EBT, 8/11/09 (Box 2)
  - H. J. Bool to EBT, 8/12/09 (Box 2)
  - Hugo Miinsterberg to EBT, 8/20/09 (Box 2)
  - L. Ollierier (?) to EBT, 8/20/09 (Box 2)
  - Scott H. Perky to EBT, 8/22/09 (Box 2)
  - J. MacKeen Cattell to EBT, 8/23/09 (Box 2)
  - Swan Sonnenschein & Co, to EBT End. statements of account, 8/27/09 (Box 2)
  - Mrs.. L. A. Pope to EBT, 8/27/09 (Box 2)
  - J. MacKeen Cattell to EBT, 8/28/09 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Nelson to EBT, 8/28/09 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Nelson to EBT, 8/31/09 (Box 2)
  - C. H. Stoelting to EBT (bills of sale), 8/ /09 (Box 2)
  - C. H. Stoelting to EBT, 9/2/09 (Box 2)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 9/18/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 9/21/09 (Box 2)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 9/23/09 (Box 2)
  - Hugo Munsterberg to EBT, 9/23/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 9/25/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 9/29/09 (Box 2)
  - R. P. Bigelow to EBT, 9/29/09 (Box 2)
  - J MacKeen Cattell to EBT, 9/29/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 10/4/09 (Box 2)
  - W. H. Pyle to EBT, 10/4/09 (Box 2)
  - C. B. Herberden to EBT End. Brasenose College brochure, 10/4/09 (Box 2)
  - J. MacKeen Cattell to EBT, 10/13/09 (Box 2)
  - M. Thomas to EBT, 10/16/09 (Box 2)
  - Josiah Royce to EBT, 10/21/09 (Box 2)
  - James Angell to EBT, 10/24/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 10/27/09 (Box 2)
  - EBT to T.A. Hunter (typed cc), 10/29/09 (Box 2)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 10/30/09 (Box 2)
  - F. Bennett to EBT, 11/1/09 (Box 2)
  - Taige Nakashima to EBT, 11/3/09 (Box 2)
  - W. H. Pyle to EBT, 11/7/09 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 11/10/09 (Box 2)
  - Hugo Mtlnsterberg to EBT, 11/12/09 (Box 2)
  - Robert M. Yerkes to EBT, 11/12/09 (Box 2)
  - Frank Wilder to EBT Encl. v list of pewter articles for sale, 11/16/09 (Box 2)
  - A. G. Bullock to EBT, 11/13/09 (Box 2)
  - Stanley Gibbons to EBT, 11/25/09 (Box 2)
  - Encl. receipt to EBT (Box 2)
  - Arthur Hadley to EBT, 12/3/09 (Box 2)
  - M. F. Washburn to EBT, 12/7/09 (Box 2)
  - Robert M. Yerkes to EBT, 12/6/09 (Box 2)
  - S (?) Geiger to EBT, 12/7/09 (Box 2)
  - H. Ogden to EBT, 12/8/09 (Box 2)
  - Russell Sarr to EBT, 12/15/09 (Box 2)
  - C. H. Stoelting to EBT End. list of apparatus for psychology experiments, 12/27/09 (Box 2)
  - Charles Bostwick to EBT, 12/29/09 (Box 2)
  - James Angell to EBT, 12/29/09 (Box 2)
  - J. Okabe to EBT, (1909?) (Box 2)
  - 1910 (Box 2)
  - G. Sakai to EBT, 1/13/10 (Box 2)
  - G. W. Harris to EBT, 1/13/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 1/13/10 (Box 2)
  - H. Be Smith to EBT, 1/14/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 1/21/10 (Box 2)
  - James Angell to EBT, 1/22/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 1/24/10 (Box 2)
  - Edmund Clark Sanford Inauguration as President of Clark College material, 2/1/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 2/2/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT (postcard), 2/3/10 (Box 2)
  - E. S. Ward to EBT, 2/4/10 (Box 2)
  - J. W. Warburton to EBT, 2/7/10 (Box 2)
  - C. B. Ponton (?) to EBT, 2/8/10 (Box 2)
  - J. Mark Baldwin to EBT, 2/8/10 (Box 2)
  - J. Mark Baldwin to EBT, 2/8/10 (Box 2)
  - E. Ward to SET, 2/10/10 (Box 2)
  - R. S. Woodworth to EBT, 2/11/10 (Box 2)
  - J. Mark Baldwin to EBTEnd. extract of letter and letter of resignation from Baldwin to Wm. James, 2/11/10 (Box 2)
  - J. Mark Baldwin to EBTEnd. extract of letter from Baldwin to William James, 2/12/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 2/14/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT (postcard), 2/14/10 (Box 2)
  - J. A. Barth to EBT, 2/19/10 German (Box 2)
  - J. F. Stout to EBT, 2/22/10 (Box 2)
  - J. McKeen Cattell to EBT, 2/24/10 (Box 2)
  - F. (?) G. Bennett to EBT, 2/2?/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 3/1/10 (Box 2)
  - Irwin to EBT, 3/1/10 (Box 2)
  - Wm. James to EBT, 3/3/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 3/3/10 (Box 2)
  - « tt »t n H, 3/3/10 Postcard (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 3/4/10 Postcard (Box 2)
  - J. Me. Cattell to EBT, 3/8/10 (Box 2)
  - J. M. Baldwin to EBT, 3/10/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Weaver to EBT, 3/10/10 (Box 2)
  - William James to John B. Watson, 3/10/10 (Box 2)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 3/11/10 (Box 2)
  - William James to EBT, 3/12/10 (Box 2)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 3/13/10 (Box 2)
  - J. McKeen Gat tell to EBT, 3/14/10 (Box 2)
  - W. B. Pillsbury to EBT, 3/15/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 3/16/10 (Box 2)
  - Wm. James to EBT, 3/16/10 (Box 2)
  - John Watson to EBT, 3/17/10 (Box 2)
  - H. W. Carr to EBT, 3/18/10 (Box 2)
  - Robert M. Yerkes to EBT, 3/18/10 (Box 2)
  - J. Mark Cattell to EBT Encl. letter from Cattell to Pierce, 3/19/10 (Box 2)
  - Wm. James to EBT, 3/19/10 (Box 2)
  - EBT to A. H. Thayer, 3/19/10 (Box 2)
  - John Watson to EBT, 3/22/10 (Box 2)
  - J. A. Leighton to EBT, 3/22/10 (Box 2)
  - Hugo Miinsterberg to EBT, 3/22/10 (Box 2)
  - W. Strunk to EBT, 3/23/10 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT Encl. letter from Hall to Wilson, 3/23/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 3/23/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Pierce to EBT, 3/24/10 (Box 2)
  - Wilson to EBT, 3/25/10 (Box 2)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 3/25/10 (Box 2)
  - J. McKeen Cattell to EBT Encl. William James to Cattell, 3/25/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 3/25/10 Postcard (Box 2)
  - W. B. Pillsbury to EBT, 3/31/10 (Box 2)
  - Olin Templin to EBT, 4/14/10 (Box 2)
  - Hubert W. Carr to EBT, 4/14/10 (Box 2)
  - Rosewell P. Angier to EBT, 4/15/10 (Box 2)
  - Arthur Daniels to EBT, 4/20/10 (Box 2)
  - Olin Templin to EBT, 4/21/10 (Box 2)
  - John Watson to EBT, 4/22/10 (Box 2)
  - Am. Phil. Invitation to EBT, 4/23/10 (Box 2)
  - W. B. Pillsbury to EBT, 4/26/10 (Box 2)
  - J. W. Baird to EBT, 4/30/10 (Box 2)
  - Rosewell P. Angier to EBT, 5/2/10 (Box 2)
  - Robert M. Yerkes to EBT, 5/2/10 (Box 2)
  - J. McKeen Cattell to EBT Encl. letter from Cattell to Pierce, 5/3/10 (Box 2)
  - J. M. Baldwin to EBT, 5/4/10 (Box 2)
  - J. H. Leuba to EBT, 5/6/10 (Box 2)
  - Wm. James to EBT, 5/8/10 (Box 2)
  - J. M. Baldwin to EBT, 5/8/10 (Box 2)
  - Gilbert Houser to EBT, 5/10/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 5/10/10 (Box 2)
  - A. S. Edwards to EBT, 5/11/10 (Box 2)
  - Olin Templin to EBT, 5/12/10 (Box 2)
  - A. Lawrence Lowell to EBT, 5/13/10 (Box 2)
  - H. A. John to EBT, 5/14/10 (Box 2)
  - H. A. John to EBT, 5/17/10 (Box 2)
  - J. McKeen Cattell to EBT, 5/17/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard C. Warren to EBT, 5/18/10 (Box 2)
  - A. Lawrence Lowell to EBT, 5/18/10 (Box 2)
  - Wm. James to EBT, 5/21/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard C. Warren to EBT, 5/23/10 (Box 2)
  - G. Moncure to EBT, 5/28/10 (Box 2)
  - Scott Perky to EBT, 5/31/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 6/3/10 (Box 2)
  - G. Moncure to EBT, 6/4/10 (Box 2)
  - Watson to EBT, 6/6/10 (Box 2)
  - Edward Ward to EBT, 6/7/10 (Box 2)
  - A. H. Pierce to EBT, 6/10/10 (Box 2)
  - James Baldwin to EBT, 6/12/10 (Box 2)
  - Tschelpanov (?) to EBT See also 10/25/24, 6/16/10 (Box 2)
  - Hugo Mitnsterberg to EBT, 6/21/10 (Box 2)
  - C. B. Herberden to EBT, 6/24/10 (Box 2)
  - R. A. Wells to EBT, 6/30/10 (Box 2)
  - Helen Clarkes to EBT, 7/2/10 (Box 2)
  - Hugo Mlinsterberg to EBT, 7/2/10 (Box 2)
  - George 3. Macomber to EBT, 7/4/10 (Box 2)
  - Stephen Colvin to EBT, 7/5/10 (Box 2)
  - J. D. Hoops to EBT, 7/6/10 (Box 2)
  - H. Brown to EBT, 7/8/10 (Box 2)
  - Watson to EBT, 7/9/10 (Box 2)
  - D. A. MacRae to EBT, 7/11/10 (Box 2)
  - V. T. Sedgwick to EBT, 7/13/10 (Box 2)
  - D. A. MacRae to EBT, 7/18/10 (Box 2)
  - H. C. Warren to EBTEnd. form letter from Psychological Review Publications, 7/23/10 (Box 2)
  - Andrew Dicks on White to EBT Encl. two petitions, 7/27/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 7/27/10 (Box 2)
  - W. H. Pyle to EBT, 7/28/10 (Box 2)
  - C. H. Stoelting to EBTEncl. 3 letters concerning purchase of laboratory equipment, 7/29/10 (Box 2)
  - Stephen Colvin to EBT, 7/30/10 (Box 2)
  - E. G. Wyckoff to EBT, 8/7/10 (Box 2)
  - S. C. S. to EBT, 8/8/10 (Box 2)
  - D. A. MacEae to SBT, 8/11/10 (Box 2)
  - H. R. Lord to EBT, 8/12/10 (Box 2)
  - J. M. Baldwin to EBT, 8/17/10 (Box 2)
  - Watson to EBT, 8/19/10 (Box 2)
  - Edward Marsh to EBT, 8/20/10 (Box 2)
  - Henry Ogden to EBT, 8/22/10 (Box 2)
  - Swan Sonnenschein & Co. to EBT Encl. statements of account, 8/23/10 (Box 2)
  - J. Mark Baldwin to EBT, 8/28/10 (Box 2)
  - Herbert Wignam, 8/30/10 (Box 2)
  - Okabe to EBT, 8/30/10 (Box 2)
  - Watson to EBT, 9/1/10 (Box 2)
  - Taiyo Nakashima to EBT, 9/7/10 (Box 2)
  - George Bristol to EBT, 9/13/10 (Box 2)
  - Margaret F. Markham to EBT, 9/l5/10 (Box 2)
  - W. T. Sedgwick to EBT, 9/15/10 (Box 2)
  - W. Peters to EBT, 9/20/10 German (Box 2)
  - J. J. Herman to EBT, 9/30/10 (Box 2)
  - Okabe to EBT, 9/??/10 (Box 2)
  - Thomas Richardson to EBT, 10/4/10 (Box 2)
  - Charles Killer to Andrews Encl. letter from Harold Goodwin to Eugene Andrews, 10/6/10 (Box 2)
  - Okabe to EBT, 10/6/10 (Box 2)
  - Robt. M. Yerkes to EBT, 10/6/10 (Box 2)
  - Edwin B. Holt to EBT, 10/9/10 (Box 2)
  - Robt. M. Yerkes to EBT, 10/10/10 (Box 2)
  - W. T. Sedgwick to EBT, 10/13/10 (Box 2)
  - H. S. Latham to EBT, 10/13/10 (Box 2)
  - W. Peter to EBT, 10/15/10 German (Box 2)
  - V. T. Sedgwick to EBT, 10/18/10 (Box 2)
  - Wm. Hoyle (?) to EBT, 10/l9/10 (Box 2)
  - Otto Kleiner (?) to EBT, 10/19/10 German (Box 2)
  - P. Chalmers Mitchell to EBT, 10/20/10 (Box 2)
  - W. B. Pillsbury to EBT End. statement of account, 10/28/10 (Box 2)
  - Charles S. Myers to EBT, 10/29/10 (Box 2)
  - W. T. Sedgwick to EBT Encl. two invitations, 10/29/10 (Box 2)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 11/1/10 (Box 2)
  - Eleanor A. Mc. C. Gamble to SBT, 11/11/10 (Box 2)
  - F. M. Urban to EBT, 11/14/10 (Box 2)
  - V. Marbe to EBT, 11/14/10 German (Box 2)
  - John Watson to EBT, 11/16/10 (Box 2)
  - G. F. Stout to EBT, 11/20/10 (Box 2)
  - Munsell to EBT, 11/25/10 (Box 2)
  - G. H. Parker (?) to EBT, 11/25/10 (Box 2)
  - Unsigned to EBT, 11/29/10 (Box 2)
  - John Watson to EBT, 11/29/10 (Box 2)
  - James Putnam to EBT, 11/29/10 (Box 2)
  - A. Lawrence Lowell to EBT, 11/29/10 (Box 2)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 12/3/10 (Box 2)
  - Wilson to EBT, 12/7/10 (Box 2)
  - Richard Walton Tully to EBT, 12/7/10 (Box 2)
  - W. T. Sedgwick to EBT, 12/8/10 (Box 2)
  - Henry Clemence to EBT, 12/8/10 (Box 2)
  - John Watson to EBT, 12/8/10 (Box 2)
  - A. D. Van Dyke, 12/8/10 (Box 2)
  - Richard Price to EBT, 12/8/lO (Box 2)
  - Otto Kleiner to EBt, 12/9/10 German (Box 2)
  - H.S. to EBT, 12/12/10 (Box 2)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 12/13/10 (Box 2)
  - J. McKeen Cattell to EBT, 12/13/10 (Box 2)
  - A.M. Pierce to EBT, 12/16/10 (Box 2)
  - George Geissler to EBT, 12/20/10 (Box 2)
  - William Hoyle to EBT, 12/21/10 (Box 2)
  - A.H. Pierce to EBT, 12/21/10 (Box 2)
  - Gilbert Houser to EBT, 12/24/10 (Box 2)
  - J. McKeen Cattell ID EBT, 12/24/10 (Box 2)
  - Undated 1910 (Box 2)
  - John Watson to EBT, 12/2 (1910?) (Box 2)
  - Gabrielle Moncure to EBT, 1910 (?) (Box 2)
  - Wilson to EBT, 1910 (?) (Box 2)
  - Mary Watson to EBT, 1910 (?) (Box 2)
  - Helen Clarke to EBT, 1910 (?) (Box 2)
  - Whipple to EBT, 1910 (?) (Box 2)
  - Herbert Cass to EBT, 1910 (?) (Box 2)
  - S.E. Hickman to EBT, 1910 (?) (Box 2)
  - Robt. M. Yerkes to EBT, ?/?/19lO (Box 2)
  - 1911E.B.Holt to EBT (Box 3)
  - Emil M(?) to EBT, 2/20/11 (Box 3)
  - Gilbert Houser to EBT, 3/2/11 (Box 3)
  - C.H. Stoetling to EBT, 3/25/11 (Box 3)
  - Sigmund Freud to EBT (in German, from Vienna); transcript, May 12, 1911 (Box 3)
  - Hugo Munsterberg to EBT, 6/6/ll (Box 3)
  - Three brochures containing the Lowell Lecture Series (Box 3)
  - * James R. Angell to J.W. Baird, enclosing a leaflet explaining the conditions of publication in the Psycho Review Series., 11/11/11 (Box 3)
  - 1912 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 2/20/12 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to H.P. Weld, 5/24,25,29; 6/1 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to Weld, 6/10/12 (Box 3)
  - J.W. Baird to EBT, 10/13/12 (Box 3)
  - 1913 (Box 3)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT (postcard), 1/27/13 (Box 3)
  - E. Ray Lancaster to A. M. Thayer, 3/12/13 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 5/27/13 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 6/2/13 (Box 3)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 6/26/13 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to H. P. Weld, 8/25/13 (Box 3)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 7/1/13 Postcard (Box 3)
  - M. (?) B. Butler to EBT, 10/16/13 (Box 3)
  - Unsigned (Thayer?) to EBT, 12/3/13 (Box 3)
  - A. H. Thayer to EBT, 12/12/13 (Box 3)
  - 1914 (Box 3)
  - A. Thayer (?) to EBT, 1/9/14 (Box 3)
  - A.H.T. to EBT, 1/10/14 (Box 3)
  - Boring to EBT, 2/19/14 (Box 3)
  - Whipple to EBT, 6/9/14 (Box 3)
  - 1915 (Box 3)
  - James R. Angell to EBT, 1/25/15 (Box 3)
  - A. Lawrence Owell to EBT, 3/3/15 (Box 3)
  - John Dewey to EBT, 5/27/15 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to H. P. Weld, 7/14, 23, 24/1915 (Box 3)
  - 1916 (Box 3)
  - * W. Bingham to Paul Thomas Young, 5/15/16 (Box 3)
  - * Edwin G. Boring to PIT, 5/15/16 (Box 3)
  - * Edwin P. Holt to PTY, 5/15/16 (Box 3)
  - * A. H. Sutherland to PTY, 5/15/16 (Box 3)
  - * Raymond Dodge to PTY, 5/15/16 (Box 3)
  - * H. P. Weld to PTY, 5/16/16 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Professor Woodworth, 6/20/16 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to H. P. Weld, 9/2/16 (Box 3)
  - Henry Rogers (?) to EBT, 12/7/16 (Box 3)
  - 1917 (Box 3)
  - S. to EBT, 1/16/17 (Box 3)
  - Mimeographed list of problems, 1/17 (Box 3)
  - Written by NEd Halt & enclosed in 11-16-18 letter; has been transferred to later date, ND 7-74 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Pillsbury, 7/8/17 (Box 3)
  - Chancey P. Biggs to EBT, 8/5/17 (Box 3)
  - R. S. Cole to EBT, 8/5/17 (Box 3)
  - Edmond C. Sanford to EBT End, clippings, 8/12/17 (Box 3)
  - Robt. M. Yerkes to EBT, 8/25/17;9/2! (Box 3)
  - Carl Seashore to EBT, 10/9/17 (Box 3)
  - Harlow Gale to EBT Encl. article "Robert Koehler and the Art League", 10/11/17 (Box 3)
  - Henry S. Williams to EBT, 10/19/17 (Box 3)
  - * Insertions made because add. material rec'd. See accession sheets. (Box 3)
  - J. W. Baird to EBT, 12/3/17 (Box 3)
  - A. B. Fitt to EBT, 12/20/17 (Box 3)
  - Henry S. Williams to EBT, 1917 (?) (Box 3)
  - 1918 (Box 3)
  - Robt. M. Yerkes to EBT, 1/8/18 (Box 3)
  - Chauncey Biggs to EBT, 1/12/18 (Box 3)
  - Robt. H. Yerkes to EBT, 1/22/18 (Box 3)
  - J. W. Baird to EBT, 1/23/18 (Box 3)
  - Robt. M. Yerkes to EBT, 1/23/18 (Box 3)
  - Karl Waugh to EBT, 1/31/18 (Box 3)
  - * Edward Bradford Titchener to Paul Thomas Young, 3/15/1918 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 3/18/18 (Box 3)
  - H, K. Wolfe to EBT, 3/29/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 4/6/18 (Box 3)
  - J. W. Baird to EBT, 4/13/18 (Box 3)
  - W. Strunk to EBT, 4/16/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 4/17/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 4/20/18 (Box 3)
  - W. 3. to EBT, 4/22/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 4/24/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 4/25/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 5/2/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 5/7/18 (Box 3)
  - John (?) to EBT, 5/7/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 5/9/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 5/17/18 (Box 3)
  - William Quinn to EBT End* article Anti- Americanism in Mexico, 5/20/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 5/23/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 5/29/18 (Box 3)
  - * insertions made because additional material rec'd. See .Accession Sheets. (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 6/6/18 (Box 3)
  - MacMillan Company to EBT End. statement of account, 7/27/18 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Alice Sullivan, 8/15/18 (Box 3)
  - Gerald Thayer to EBT End, pamphlet Camouflage in War and Nature, 8/29/18 (Box 3)
  - Gerald Thayer to EBT, 0/12/18 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Pillsbury, 10/17/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 10/31/19 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 11/5/18 (Box 3)
  - Taizo Nakashima to EBT, 11/10/18 (Box 3)
  - Mimeographed bulletin, 11/12/18 (Box 3)
  - Ned Holt to EBT, 11/16/18 (Box 3)
  - Gerald Thayer to EBT, 12/3/18 (Box 3)
  - Jacques Soel to B. F. Kingsbury, 12/3/18 (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 12/22/18 (Box 3)
  - C. S. Meyers to EBT, 12/26/18 (Box 3)
  - George Bartlett to EBT, 12/27/13 (Box 3)
  - Statements of account from George Alien and Unwin, 12/31/18 (Box 3)
  - 1919 (Box 3)
  - Hugh Rayburn to EBT, 1/2/19 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to Paul Thomas Young, 1/5/1919 (Box 3)
  - Ned Holt to EBT, 1/23/19 (Box 3)
  - C. Smith to EBT, 1/23/19 (Box 3)
  - R. S. Cole to EBT, H/26/19 (Box 3)
  - Halla A. Miller to EBT, 1/27/19 (Box 3)
  - C. F. Taensch to EBT, 1/29/19 (Box 3)
  - * insertions made because acid, material rec'd. See accession sheets. (Box 3)
  - Carl Seashore to EBT, 1/31/19 (Box 3)
  - C. F. Taensch to EBT, 2/6/19 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 2/7/19 (Box 3)
  - R. S. Cole to EBT, 2/8/19 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 2/11/19 (Box 3)
  - Barbara Sparks Baird to EBT, 2/25/19 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Woodworth, 3/15/19 (Box 3)
  - R. Yerkes to EBT, 3/20/19 (Box 3)
  - Ned Holt to EBT, 3/24/19 (Box 3)
  - R. Yerkes to EBT, 3/27/19 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Dr. Elliot, 4/4/19 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Paul T. Young, 4/4/19 (Box 3)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 4/4/l9 (Box 3)
  - Gilbert Rich to EBT, 4/5/19 (Box 3)
  - C. H. Thurber to EBT, 5/3/19 (Box 3)
  - Charles Soreny to EBT, 5/7/19 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 5/8/19 (Box 3)
  - H. Lesage to EBT, 5/17/19 French (Box 3)
  - Goodspeed's Book Shop to EBT, 5/21/19 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Paul T. Young, 5/24/19 (Box 3)
  - A. B. Fitt to EBT, 5/26/19 (Box 3)
  - H. D. Brackett to EBT End. postcard from Mr.. Oldfather to Brackett, 6/6/19 (Box 3)
  - (?) Clap (?) to EBT, 6/9/19 (Box 3)
  - Wells College Announcement, 6/13/19 (Box 3)
  - C. F. Loreny to EBT, 6/17/19 (Box 3)
  - Adelaide F. Cohen to EBT, 6/23/19 (Box 3)
  - C. Bostwick to EBT, 6/25/19 (Box 3)
  - Dr. M. Matsermoto, 7/16/19 (Box 3)
  - G. F. Stout to EBT, 7/17/19 (Box 3)
  - F. M. Urban to EBT, 7/24/19 (Box 3)
  - MacMillan Company to EBT, 7/27/19 (Box 3)
  - Charles Loreny to EBT, 8/6/19 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Paul T. Young, 8/18/19 (Box 3)
  - Edward Bernays to EBT, 11/19/19 (Box 3)
  - Felix Alcan to EBT, 11/20/19 (Box 3)
  - C. H. Stoelting to EBT, 11/22/19 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 12/8/19 (Box 3)
  - R.M. Ogden to EBT, 12/17/19 (Box 3)
  - R.M. Ogden to EBT, 12/27/19 (Box 3)
  - George Alien and Unwin to EBT, 12/31/19 (Box 3)
  - Mimeograph problem, 1919 (?) (Box 3)
  - 1920 (Box 3)
  - R. M. Ogden to EBT, 1/5/20 (Box 3)
  - G. W. Young to EBT, 1/7/20 (Box 3)
  - R. M. Ogden to EBT, 1/7/20 (Box 3)
  - C. S. layers to EBT, 1/10/20 (Box 3)
  - L. A. Pichstein to EBT, 2/4/20 (Box 3)
  - M. J. Zigler to EBT, 2/8/20 (Box 3)
  - Lightner Witmer to EBT, 2/12/20 (Box 3)
  - Jacob Gould Schurman to EBT, 2/17/20 (Box 3)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 3/23/20 (Box 3)
  - Shepard Franz to EBT, 4/1/20 (Box 3)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 4/8/20 (Box 3)
  - H. 3. to EBT, 4/10/20 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 4/22/20 (Box 3)
  - J. K. Sharzha to EBT Encl. article manuscript, 4/30/20 (Box 3)
  - A. Thayer to EBT, 5/4/20 (Box 3)
  - E. G, Boring to EBT, 6/23/20 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to Paul T. Young, 7/1/20 (Box 3)
  - A. H. Martin to EBT6, 7/5/20 (Box 3)
  - ??? Macon, 7/10/20 (Box 3)
  - John Wallace Pellenbach to EBT, 7/27/20 (Box 3)
  - 3. Takaki to EBT, 7/30/20 (Box 3)
  - Macmillan to EBT End. statement of account, 8/11/20 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Dr. Feldman, 9/14/20 (Box 3)
  - C. R. Potter to EBT, 10/19/20 (Box 3)
  - Jacob Rothschild to EBT, 11/1/20 (Box 3)
  - Statement of account to EBT from Corning Glass, 11/12/20 (Box 3)
  - G. E. Moore to EBT, 11/17/20 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 12/6/20 (Box 3)
  - George Alien and Unwin to EBT, 12/31/20 (Box 3)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 1920 (?) (Box 3)
  - Macmillan to EBT, 1920 (?) (Box 3)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 1Q20 (?) (Box 3)
  - 1921 (Box 3)
  - A. Franklin Shull to EBT, 1/7/21 (Box 3)
  - Karl Dallenbach to EBT, 1/10/21 (Box 3)
  - James Edwin Creighton, 1/26/21 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Miss Comstock, 3/7/21 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Miss Comstock, 3/15/21 (Box 3)
  - Karl Dallanbach to EBT, 4/4/21 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to H.P. Weld, 4/22/21 (Box 3)
  - Raymond Dodge to EBT, 5/3/21 (Box 3)
  - Pillsbury to EBT, 5/17/21 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Miss Comstock, 5/23/21 (Box 3)
  - C. H. Stoelting to EBT, 5/28/21 (Box 3)
  - Pillsbury to H.P. Weld, 6/6/21 (Box 3)
  - R. W. Macon to EBT, 6/3/21 (Box 3)
  - * EBT to H.P. Weld, 6/30/21 (Box 3)
  - W. G. Smith to EBT, 7/12/21 (Box 3)
  - Maemillan Company to EBT, 7/29/21 (Box 3)
  - J. Baldwin to EBT, 8/29/21 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Dimmick, 9/12/21 (Box 3)
  - H* W. Thayer to EBT * EBT to H.P. Weld EBT to Alice Sullivan, 9/18/21 9/18/21 9/24/21 (Box 3)
  - Alexander Graham Bell to EBT, 9/29/21 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Mrs.. F. L. Dimmick, 10/6/21 (Box 3)
  - Gerald Thayer to EBT, 10/12/21 (Box 3)
  - H. S. (??) to EBT, 10/17/21 (Box 3)
  - Fauberger to EBT, 10/20/21 (Box 3)
  - Howard C. Warren to EBT, 10/21/21 (Box 3)
  - N. Tsch to EBT, 10/25/21 German (Box 3)
  - Adolf Meyer to EBT, 10/26/21 (Box 3)
  - £. G. Boring to EBT, 10/28/21 (Box 3)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 11/3/21 (Box 3)
  - R. W. Macon to EBT, 11/6/21 (Box 3)
  - Paul Brockett to EBT, 11/9/21 (Box 3)
  - R. R. Smith to EBT, 12/1/21 (Box 3)
  - EBT to Mrs.. Dimmick, 12/6/21 (Box 3)
  - Henry Head (?) to EBT, 12/12/21 (Box 3)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 12/15/21 (Box 3)
  - Joseph Jastrow to SET, 12/21/(21)? (Box 3)
  - G. E. Muller to EBT, 12/29/21 (Box 3)
  - Howard Warren to EBT, 12/29/21 (Box 3)
  - 1922 (Box 4)
  - E. C. S. to EBT, 1/2/22 (Box 4)
  - James Ward to EBT, 1/2/22 (Box 4)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 1/4/22 (Box 4)
  - Charles Gardner to EBT, 1/9/22 (Box 4)
  - Karl Dallenbach to EBT, 1/11/22 (Box 4)
  - G. Horning (?) to EBT, 1/20/22 German (Box 4)
  - Lyman H. Low to EBT, 1/27/22 (Box 4)
  - Rosewell P. Angier to EBT, 2/1/22 (Box 4)
  - Max Eastman to EBT, 2/2/22 (Box 4)
  - Sarah Fuertes H (?) to EBT End. newspaper clipping, 2/20/22 (Box 4)
  - E. G. Boring to EBT, 2/24/22 (Box 4)
  - H. B. Davis to EBT, 2/24/22 (Box 4)
  - G. Stanley Hall to EBT, 2/24/22 (Box 4)
  - Felix Krueger to EBT, 3/13/22 German (Box 4)
  - EBT to Alice Sullivan, 3/14/22 (Box 4)
  - John B. Watson to EBT, 3/14/22 (Box 4)
  - Mrs.. C. K. Freeman to EBT, 3/19/22 (Box 4)
  - E. Bucets to EBT, 3/23/22 (Box 4)
  - Southern Tier Electrical Supply to EBT, 3/24/22 (Box 4)
  - T, A. Hunter to EBT, 4/12/22 (Box 4)
  - Dodge to EBT, 4/20/22 (Box 4)
  - Charles Bostwick to EBT, 4/29/22 (Box 4)
  - Forrest Dimmick to EBT, 5/8/22 (Box 4)
  - H. A. B (?) to EBT, 5/12/22 (Box 4)